Contact

aparnanupur975@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/aparnasingh-7b047716b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Programming
Microsoft Office
Microsoft Excel

Languages

English (Full Professional) Hindi (Native or Bilingual)

Publications

Research article on Placement Prediction

APARNA SINGH

Associate Software Engineer at Accenture South Delhi

Summary

Experienced Associate Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, Computer Science, C++, Databases, and Public Speaking. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused in Information Technology from Maharaja Agrasen Institute Of Technology.

Experience

Accenture
Associate Software Engineer
October 2018 - Present (1 year 11 months)
Gurugram

BSES Delhi App Developer June 2017 - July 2017 (2 months) New Delhi

Developed an android app to measure the loss reduction in electricity supply.

Kavitha Seeds Private Ltd. Intern July 2016 - August 2016 (2 months) Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh, India

Education

Maharaja Agrasen Institute Of Technology
Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Information Technology · (2014 - 2018)

LBS RK Puram, New Delhi Intermediate, Science · (2012 - 2016)

FIITJEE

Mathematics and Science · (2012 - 2014)

St. John's School, Tulsipur, Ghazipur High School, Science · (2008 - 2012)